timwe.com 2018-11-26

# TIMWE

PRIVACY POLICY ACCORDING TO THE REGULATION (EU) 2016/679 OF THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND OF THE COUNCIL of 27 April 2016 

 The present privacy policy is rendered by TIMWE Group as a Data Owner according to article 2 number 1 of the 2016/679 OF THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND OF THE COUNCIL of 27 April 2016.   

**Your Privacy Rights**   

This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, storage, and protection of your personal information. It applies to the www.timwe.com website (hereinafter “Website”), and all related applications, tools, service and events regardless of how you access or use them. You accept this Privacy Policy when you access to the Website or use any features, technologies, functions or services offered on it. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our Website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. This policy relates to our privacy practices in connection with this Website and any TIMWE Group events. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites you may access from any link inserted in the Website. For sake of clarity, any use of the TIMWE Group Website automatically comprehends the acceptance of this Privacy Policy.  

**How we collect information about you**   

As a visitor, you do not have to submit any personal information in order to use the Website. This Website only collects personal information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by visitors. Such information may consist of, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address and telephone. Regarding the Newsletter subscription, with your consent, your name, email and company name, will be properly stored and privately handled, according to the General Data Protection Regulation. The email address you provide for subscription processing, maybe used to send you information and updates pertaining our services, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service info. If at any time, you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed  unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each mail.

**How we use personal information and cookies**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure and efficient experience. You may provide personal information via this Website, for example, to gain access to specific content, attend a hosted event, respond to a survey, or request communications about specific areas of interest. In such cases, the information you submit will be used to manage your request and to customize and improve this Website and related services offered to you. Nevertheless, we may use your personal information for marketing purposes, or to send you promotional materials or communications regarding services provided by entities within TIMWE Group that we feel may be of interest to you.   Your personal information may also be used to protect our rights or property and that of our users and, where appropriate, to comply with legal process.   This website collects standard internet log information including your IP address, browser type and language, access times, and referring website addresses.  

**How we share personal information with other parties**

TIMWE Group shall not share your personal data with third parties except with government officials, or other third parties pursuant to a court order, or other legal process or requirement applicable to TIMWE Group or one of its clients, suppliers and partners; when we need to do so in order to to comply with law; or when we believe that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations of our rights. TIMWE Group will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.

**How we use cookies and technical information   **

To ensure that this Website is well managed and to facilitate improved navigation, we may also use cookies (small text files stored in a user’s browser) to collect aggregate data. Additional information on how we use cookies and other tracking technologies and how you can control these can be found in our Cookies Policy.  

**How we protect and store personal information   **

Throughout this policy, we use the term “personal information” to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous so that it does not identify a specific user. We store and process your personal information on our computers. We protect your information using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration.  

According to the 67/98 law of the 26th October – Protection of Personal Data, you can at any time exercise the following rights: 1. Obtain information of all personal data collection; 2. Obtain the access of the confirmation of the data treatment, correction or annulment of data that does not follow the law, in the case of processing of personal data related to the national security and criminal prevention or investigation, the right of access is exercised through the CNPD or another independent authority; 3. Obtain the right to object and oppose, in full or in part, to data processing for legitimate reasons, even if personal data are relevant to the purposes of the data collecting.  

**How we answer visitors’ questions**   

If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy while using this Website, please contact us.
